You're a number two pencil and you think, well, but I mean, it's like you don't even know who you are.
And the boring guys are f***ing up for the good guys.
The same way the s*** guys who are pretending to be good guys are f***ing up for the good guys.
Because I be trying to tell the good guys.
So when the good guys be like, oh, the women don't like good guys.
It's like you have to understand the f*** is showing up looking just like you.
So you can't blame women for not trusting it on face value.
Because ultimately these cats be really doing well with the face mask off.
Okay.
There's a lot of code switching in a whole different way going on.
But the boring dudes, they be just trying to ride on like, I'm nice.
I'm nice.